Digital Collections and Archives Records UA069
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Exhibit-related materials, 1940 -- 2013; 2005 -- 2007; UA069.007; 7.75 Linear Feet
  - Tufts College: A Wartime Campus [3 of 6], 2000 -- 2001; UA069.007.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College: A Wartime Campus [4 of 6], 2000 -- 2001; UA069.007.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College: A Wartime Campus [5 of 6], 2000 -- 2001; UA069.007.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College: A Wartime Campus [6 of 6], 2000 -- 2001; UA069.007.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Back to the Hill: 2005 reunion exhibit [1 of 2], UA069.007.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Back to the Hill: 2005 Reunion [2 of 2], UA069.007.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Greek Life: Life on the Hill 2005 Exhibit [1 of 2], UA069.007.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Greek Life: Life on the Hill 2005 Exhibit [2 of 2], UA069.007.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Reunion Exhibit Spring 2006 [1 of 3], UA069.007.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Reunion Exhibit Spring 2006 [2 of 3], UA069.007.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Reunion Exhibit Spring 2006 [3 of 3], UA069.007.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Shattering the Great Divide: Sports and Gender at Tufts University Exhibit [1 of 4], 2006; UA069.007.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Shattering the Great Divide: Sports and Gender at Tufts University Exhibit [2 of 4], 2006; UA069.007.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Atomic Veterans exhibit [1 of 2], 2011; UA069.007.001.00016 (Box 6)
    The Atomic Veterans exhibit was installed in August 2011 by MacKenzie Brigham, Collections and Reference Assistant. The exhibit was taken down in January 2012 and replaced by the spring 2012 reunion exhibit, installed by Molly Bruce, Collections and Reference Assistant.
  - Atomic Veterans exhibit [2 of 2], 2011; UA069.007.001.00017 (Box 6)
  - Shattering the Great Divide: Sports and Gender at Tufts University Exhibit [3 of 4], 2006; UA069.007.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Shattering the Great Divide: Sports and Gender at Tufts University Exhibit [4 of 4], 2006; UA069.007.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Archival Traces: Muriel Simonson at Jackson College, 1924-1929 [1 of 4], 2007; UA069.007.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Archival Traces: Muriel Simonson at Jackson College, 1924-1929 [2 of 4], 2007; UA069.007.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Archival Traces: Muriel Simonson at Jackson College, 1924-1929 [3 of 4], 2007; UA069.007.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Archival Traces: Muriel Simonson at Jackson College, 1924-1929 [4 of 4], 2007; UA069.007.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Reunion '02 and '07 Exhibit [1 of 4], 2007; UA069.007.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Reunion '02 and '07 Exhibit [2 of 4], 2007; UA069.007.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Reunion '02 and '07 Exhibit [3 of 4], 2007; UA069.007.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Reunion '02 and '07 Exhibit [4 of 4], 2007; UA069.007.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Fragments of the Past, Fall 2007 Exhibit [1 of 2], UA069.007.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Fragments of the Past, Fall 2007 Exhibit [2 of 2], UA069.007.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Multiple Exhibit Images [1 of 3], 2006; UA069.007.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Multiple Exhibit Images [2 of 3], 2006; UA069.007.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Multiple Exhibit Images [3 of 3], 2006; UA069.007.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Lighting up the hill: 03/08 reunion classes exhibit [1 of 3], 2008; UA069.007.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Lighting up the hill: 03/08 reunion classes exhibit [2 of 3], 2008; UA069.007.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Lighting up the hill: 03/08 reunion classes exhibit [3 of 3], UA069.007.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - African American History at Tufts Exhibit, 1940 -- 2002; UA069.007.003 (Box 3)
    Materials collected by and in conjunction with Professor Gerald Gill and the Tufts history department. Consists of secondary source materials, photographs and exhibit pieces. Box 1 of 3
  - African American History at Tufts Exhibit, 1940 -- 2002; UA069.007.004 (Box 4)
    Materials collected by and in conjunction with Professor Gerald Gill and the Tufts history department. Consists of secondary source materials, photographs and exhibit pieces. Box 2 of 3
  - African American History at Tufts Exhibit, 1940 -- 2002; UA069.007.005 (Box 5)
    Materials collected by and in conjunction with Professor Gerald Gill and the Tufts history department. Consists of secondary source materials, photographs and exhibit pieces. Box 3 of 3
  - Tufts theater history, 1910s-1960s, fall 2008 exhibit [1 of 5], UA069.007.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Tufts theater history, 1910s-1960s, fall 2008 exhibit [2 of 5], UA069.007.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Tufts theater history, 1910s-1960s, fall 2008 exhibit [3 of 5], UA069.007.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Tufts theater history, 1910s-1960s, fall 2008 exhibit [4 of 5], UA069.007.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Tufts theater history, 1910s-1960s, fall 2008 exhibit [5 of 5], UA069.007.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Edward R. Murrow Papers: brochure and postcard, 2008; UA069.007.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Reunion Classes Exhibit, 1959-2004, sping 2009 [1 of 4], UA069.007.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Reunion Classes Exhibit, 1959-2004, spring 2009 [2 of 4], UA069.007.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Reunion Classes Exhibit, 1959-2004, spring 2009 [3 of 4], UA069.007.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Reunion Classes Exhibit, 1959-2004, spring 2009 [4 of 4], UA069.007.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - John A. Holmes and NROTC exhibits, fall 2009, UA069.007.006.00011 (Box 6)
    The John A. Holmes and NROTC exhibits were installed in August 2009 by Laura Cutter, casual employee. The Holmes exhibit was taken down in January 2010 and replaced by the spring exhibit, installed by MacKenzie Brigham, casual employee. The NROTC exhibit remained on display through spring 2010, since the NROTC class (1945) was having their 55th reunion in 2010. The exhibit was altered slightly to make it more general and less specifically focused on Jason Samuels and Andrew Lentine. The material from the NROTC portion of the exhibit will be processed with material from the spring 2010 exhibit.
    Laura Cutter 2010-01-22
  - John A. Holmes exhibit, fall 2009, UA069.007.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - John A. Holmes exhibit, fall 2009, UA069.007.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - NROTC at Tufts 1941-1972 exhibit, 2009 -- 2010; UA069.007.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Reunion classes exhibit, 1965-2005 [1 of 3], 2010; UA069.007.006.00015 (Box 6)
    The 2010 reunion classes exhibit was installed in January 2010 by MacKenzie Brigham, casual employee. The reunion exhibit was taken down in August 2010 and replaced by the fall exhibit, installed by Susanne Belovari, Archivist for Reference and Collections.
  - Reunion classes exhibit, 1965-2005 [2 of 3], 2010; UA069.007.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Reunion classes exhibit, 1965-2005 [3 of 3], 2010; UA069.007.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Reunion classes exhibit, 1961-2001 [1 of 3], 2011; UA069.007.006.00018 (Box 6)
    The 2011 reunion classes exhibit was installed in January 2011 by Derek Mosley, casual employee. The reunion exhibit was taken down in August 2011 and replaced by the fall exhibit, installed by MacKenzie Brigham, casual employee.
  - Reunion classes exhibit, 1961-2001 [2 of 3], 2011; UA069.007.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Reunion classes exhibit, 1961-2001 [3 of 3], 2011; UA069.007.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Myron J. Files exhibit [1 of 4], 2011; UA069.007.006.00021 (Box 6)
    The Myron J. Files exhibit was installed in August 2011 by MacKenzie Brigham, Collections and Reference Assistant. The exhibit was taken down in January 2012 and replaced by the spring 2012 reunion exhibit, installed by Molly Bruce, Collections and Reference Assistant.
  - Myron J. Files exhibit [2 of 4], 2011; UA069.007.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Myron J. Files exhibit [3 of 4], 2011; UA069.007.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Myron J. Files exhibit [4 of 4], 2011; UA069.007.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Reunion classes exhibit [1 of 2], 2012; UA069.007.007.00001 (Box 7)
    Exhibit signs and labels, as well as reproductions of photographs focusing on Reunion classes. This exhibit was installed in January 2012 and taken down in August 2012.
  - Reunion classes exhibit [2 of 2], 2012; UA069.007.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Ellen Lutz Exhibit - Fall 2012 [1 of 3], UA069.007.007.00003 (Box 7)
    Exhibit signs and labels, as well as reproductions of photographs focusing on the Ellen Lutz Papers (MS177). This exhibit was installed in in August 2012 and taken down in January 2013.
  - Ellen Lutz Exhibit - Fall 2012 [2 of 3], UA069.007.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Ellen Lutz Exhibit - Fall 2012 [3 of 3], UA069.007.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Open Access at Tufts Exhibit - Fall 2012, UA069.007.007.00006 (Box 7)
    Exhibit signs and labels, as well as reproductions of photographs and radiographs focusing on open access scholarship at Tufts. Exhibit material collected by Dr. Mark Pokras. This exhibit was installed in in August 2012 and taken down in January 2013.
  - Fall Exhibits - Oversize, 2012; UA069.007.007.00007 (Box Shared 1)
    Oversize items relating to the Ellen Lutz and Open Access exhibits from Fall 2012.
  - Reunion Classes Exhibit, Spring [1 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.008.00001 (Box 8)
    Exhibit signs and labels, as well as reproductions of photographs, correspondence, and digital objects from DCA's collections. This exhibit was installed by Sarah Gustafson, graduate assistant, in January 2013 and taken down by Tim Walsh, graduate assistant, on August 26, 2013.
  - Reunion Classes Exhibit, Spring [2 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Reunion Classes Exhibit, Spring [3 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Reunion Classes Exhibit, Spring [4 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Reunion Classes Exhibit, Spring [5 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Reunion Classes Exhibit, Spring [6 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Jester Hairston exhibit [1 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.009.00001; Digital Collections and Archives (Box 9)
    Exhibit boards and labels created for the exhibit, "Jester Hairston, A29: He and His Talents Prevailed." The exhibit was curated and installed by Tim Walsh, graduate assistant, in August 2013 and taken down by Leah Edelman, graduate assistant, on January 7, 2014. Materials include reproductions of photographs and correspondence from DCA's collections.
    Hairston, Jester
  - Jester Hairston exhibit [2 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.009.00002; Digital Collections and Archives (Box 9)
  - Jester Hairston exhibit [3 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.009.00003; Digital Collections and Archives (Box 9)
  - Jester Hairston exhibit [4 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.009.00004; Digital Collections and Archives (Box 9)
  - Jester Hairston exhibit [5 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.009.00005; Digital Collections and Archives (Box 9)
  - Jester Hairston exhibit [6 of 6], 2013; UA069.007.009.00006; Digital Collections and Archives (Box 9)
  - DCA collections posters from Tisch lobby and hallway, circa 2010 -- 2012; UA069.007.033; .1 Linear Feet (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 1)
    Four posters for DCA collections: John Holmes, World Peace Foundation, Edward Murrow, V-12.
    Transferred by Tisch staff, 2018, accession UA-2018-032.